

9

Chapel Hill, QLD 4069

C

0403 861 169

 \geq

kate@gerber.id.au

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Statement of Attainment

Responsible Service of Alcohol Hospitality Institute of Australasia, Brisbane, QLD September 2018

Diploma of Beauty Therapy

Beauty Therapy Australian National College of Beauty, Brisbane, QLD August 2014

KATE GERBER

SUMMARY

Hardworking employee with customer service, multitasking and time management abilities. Devoted to giving every customer a positive and memorable experience.

- 5+ years experience in retail/customer service roles
- 3+ years experience in glassy/bartending/waitressing roles
- ~7 months experience in administration role

SKILLS

- Outstanding Customer Service
- Critical Thinking
- Team Building
- Friendly, Positive Attitude
- Reliable & Trustworthy

- · Organizational Ability
- Professional and Mature
- Articulate and Well-Spoken
- Well Presented

EXPERIENCE

ENGRAVING WORKSHOP MANAGER

Valley Engraving | Albion, QLD | September 2021 - April 2022

- Greeted and assisted customers to foster positive experiences.
- Assisted with customer requests and answered questions to improve satisfaction.
- Maintained clean and neat work area to maximize productivity and prevent errors.
- Supervised use, maintenance and replacement of workshop tools, equipment and materials.
- Produced sales documents, finalized deals and filed records.
- Used Gravostyle 8 and IS8000 engraving systems to complete custom work.
- Machine-engraved merchandise for customers.

BARTENDER/RESTAURANT WAITRESS

Bracken Ridge Tavern | Bracken Ridge, QLD | November 2018 - July 2021

- Operated cash register and Point of Sale (POS) system for transactions.
- Mixed and served both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks for patrons by following standard recipes and procedures.

- Checked identification of guests to verify age requirements for alcohol purchase.
- Maintained knowledge of bar and menu options to prepare drinks and make food recommendations.
- Recommended food and drinks to patrons based on preference and special promotions.
- Maintained spotless, well-stocked bar organized and ready for customer demands.
- Cleaned bar and table surfaces throughout shift to help reduce risk of pathogens.
- Removed, washed and polished empty glasses, took plates to kitchen and discarded trash.
- Took food and drinks to bar and table customers.
- Sliced and pitted fruit used to garnish drinks.
- Washed and sanitized plates using industrial dishwashers according to manufacturer instructions.
- Communicated with hosts, bussers and kitchen staff to prepare for and serve customers.

GLASSY/BARBACK

The Brightside | Fortitude Valley, Qld | July 2018 - November 2018

- Maintained spotless, well-stocked bar organized and ready for customer demands.
- Cleaned bar and table surfaces throughout shift to help reduce risk of pathogens.
- Removed and disposed of bags from trash receptacles in entire venue.
- Removed, washed and polished empty glasses.
- Cleaned bathrooms spills where needed and resupplied with proper paper products.
- Effectively multitasked within fast-paced environment.
- Made friendly conversation with customers to provide enjoyable bar experience.
- Cleaned up spills and broken glassware and safely disposed of sharp pieces.
- Worked in close collaboration with team members to ensure customers received high-quality service.

GLASSY/FOOD RUNNER

Blute's Bar | Fortitude Valley, QLD | May 2018 - November 2018

- Double-checked meals placed in window against customer tickets for accuracy.
- Memorized dining room floor plans and understood seat number system.
- Assisted servers to optimize guest dining experience.
- Responded quickly to customer concerns and escalated major issues to management.
- Removed dishes and glasses from tables or counters to take to kitchen for cleaning.

- Stocked service supply areas with tableware, garnishes and prepared food.
- Effectively multitasked within fast-paced environment.
- Made friendly conversation with customers to provide enjoyable bar experience.
- Cleaned up spills and broken glassware and safely disposed of sharp pieces.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Please contact me via email or text, as I have difficulties hearing over the phone. Thank you for your time and consideration!